Will you eat one more paratha? Come on, we have to
go to school, right?
[Music]
Hello
[Music] Come on, come on
[
Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
Bhaiya, what should I cook for dinner, Didi is
not picking up the phone.
[Music]
Thank you, you do
n't get the claim settlement money,
what are you doing to the insurance, what are you
doing to everyone?
[Music]
Sharma ji's son has bought a sweet shop.
[Music] He has
invited us for the inauguration today, we both are getting
late. [
Music]
You don't know Bhaiya, after Papa's death, we had nothing, we had a
child. I did
n't even know that Papa had a life
insurance policy,
but Supriya Didi got the claim settled so quickly
that today we are able to stand on our own feet.
[Music]